-Good morning!   -Hi.
-早上好!   -嗨.
Welcome back.
欢迎回来.
Did you have a good trip?
旅行愉快吗?
Wonderful. Wonderful and very productive.
很棒. 很棒并且很有成果
You didn't work the whole time, did you?
你没有一直在工作, 对不对?
No. We had time to explore.
No. 我们有时间去探索.
We wandered around Prague quite a bit.
我们在布拉格闲逛了不少.
What a city.
多美的一座城市.
It's supposed to be beautiful.
它应该是很美的.
It is.
确实如此.
The hotel was right in the center of the old city.
酒店就在老城的中心.
We walked everywhere. We shopped.
我们到处走. 我们购物.
We went to some fine restaurants.
我们去了一些很好的餐厅.
But even better,
但更好的是,
we went to a little lake.
我们去了一个小湖边.
Where?
哪里?
About 60 miles northwest of Prague.
大概60英里 布拉格的西北方.
Near Karlovy Vary.
靠近Karlovy Vary.
It was surrounded by farms and forests.
它被农场和森林包围着.
And hills too,
还有山,
though they weren't very high.
不过它们不是很高.
We had a wonderful picnic.
我们享用了一个美妙的野餐.
No one was there but us.
那儿一个人都没有 除了我们.
Did you work at all?
你到底工作了没有?
Oh yes.
You and I can talk about that right now.
你和我可以谈谈关于那个 马上.
You don't have plans for lunch, do you?
你没有计划对于午餐, 对吗?
Time to go.
该走了.